# Davies Obaro Okpeta

## Software Developer

Phone: 07043901625 Linkedn: @daviesOkpeta

E-mail: thenerfsenpai@gmail.com Github: @Nefario3k

Portfolio: thenerfsenpai

A software developer with over **5years** of experience specializing in software development for websites, webapps and database structure and maintenance. I can implement seamless content management systems from managing estate housing to financial institutions. My greatest strength is team management, client engagement and dedication to task assigned to the team.

# Experience

#### Dec 2020 - Feb 2021

#### **Frontend Web Developer**

Udemy

- Acquired skills and certifications relating to frontend web development.
- Built functional webapps and websites with beginner userfriendly UI designs using HTML, CSS, and vanilla JavaScript.
- Improved website performance by implementing search engine optimization techniques.

#### Feb 2022 - Oct 2024

#### **Software Developer**

**Bex-it Digital Solutions** 

- Developed and maintained software applications using a variety of programming languages.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure timely and successful project delivery.
- Improved the efficiency of the software development process through the implementation of automated testing and SOPs.
- Responsible for all content management system development.
- Responsible for team engagement for successful delivery.
- Client engagement for clear cut communication of specified goals and requirement for projects.

#### Aug 2023 - present

#### **Frontend Web Developer**

**THCO** 

- Developed and maintained AI driven technologies working with languages such as Ruby
- Implemented and maintained from start to production an Al driven recruiting platform, offering key employee search and data management.
- Implemented email systems and campaigns to send, manage and offer users better recruiter experience.
- Responsible for all advanced styling, animation, logic and

fetch automation.

 Responsible for all user and admin ended app including app, admin and job-boards.

#### Jan 2024 - present

#### **Software Engineer**

Tiqwa

- Maintained and improved the administrative section of the travel agency for multitenancy for multiple distinct apps.
- Implemented new styles, animations and JS logics to give applike feel to the web apps
- Responsible for creating, implementing designs and crossplatform testing of email structures for multiple email templates.
- Responsible for all advanced styling, animation, logic and fetch automation.
- Responsible for all user and admin ended app including app, admin and emails.

## Education

#### August 2016

Daniellina

#### **Bachelor of Science in Applied Mathematics**

Federal University, Otuoke

- Graduated summa cum laude.
- Created a system to calculate the effect of lipoprotein concentration on M.H.D blood flow through parallel plate with heat source and magnetic intensity.

# **Recent Projects**

Beeziing	Beeziing
	Digital card app builder and socials app.
Savings Box	Savings Box

eCommerce platform for loans, savings, investments etc.

D = ==1:...

<u>Korner</u> Korner

eCommerce platform for beauty products.

Tiqwa
Tiqwa
Travel agency, supplying api's, webapp and custom templates

RealtimePay RealtimePay

Utility webapp for online utility bills payment with modern aesthetics.

TalenAi

Ai powered recruiting platform, job board posting and hosting, and Ai employee creation and management.

## **Skills**

Modern JavaScript	<ul><li>Understanding of ECMAScript 6+</li><li>Web api's</li></ul>
Version control	Git and Git workflows
Server-Side Rendering (SSR)	Experience with nuxtjs and nextjs
Testing and debugging	Experience with jest and dev tools
Performance Optimization	<ul><li>Code spitting</li><li>Lazy loading</li><li>Image optimization</li></ul>
State Management	<ul><li>Redux</li><li>Vuex</li><li>Pinia</li></ul>
Client Side	React, Vue, Nuxt, Next, Express, etc.
Server Side	Nuxt, Next, Php, Laravel, Node
Data Management	MongoDB, SQL

# **Certifications**

2021-02 Full-stack Web developer

**2022-01** LFD – Laravel full-stack developer

## References

## Ibidapo Adeolu.

Webastry Designs, 34 Shettima Alli Monguno Crescent, Utako District, FCT Abuja Nigeria. Contact: **LinkedIn**  Paul White.

Bex-it Digital Solutions, No 9 Star Lake Close, Maitama. FCT Abuja Nigeria. Contact: **LinkedIn**  Osaro Igbinovia.

Resplash Inc., Lagos Nigeria. Contact: **LinkedIn**